

TEE WENJIE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

https://github.com/wenjietee linkedin.com/in/tee-wenjie

wenjietj@gmail.com +65 9365 4413 Singaporean

EDUCATION

General Assembly,

Software Engineering Immersive Nov 2021 - Jun 2021

Digipen Institute of Technology,

B.F.A, Digital Art and Animation

Sep 2013 - Apr 2017

Nanyang Polytechnic,

Diploma in Digital Media Design (Animation) Jan 2006- Sep 2009

SKILLS

Tools and Technologies:

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python, ReactJS, ExpressJS, NodeJS, JQuery, Django, AJAX, Bootstrap MaterialUI

Deployment:

Git, Github, Heroku,

Databases:

MongoDB, PostgreSQL

Methodologies:

OOP, MVC, REST, Authentication, User Stories, Agile, Scrum, Responsive Design, Wireframing

Digital Content Creation:

3D modeling, 3D animation, Digital Painting, Compositing, Photoshop, 3ds Max, Zbrush, After Effects, Premiere Pro

SUMMARY

Aspiring Software Engineer with 4 years of 3D content creation and integrating digital assets in simulators. I bridge the domains of art and code to ensure the content is delivered with the artist's vision while preserving performance.

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING PROJECTS

WiVolunteer

WiVolunteer is a web application that enables the user to join and organize volunteering events. It aims to improve volunteering events with analysis of feedbacks from participants.

ExpressJS, JWT, Mongoose, MomentJS, Nodemailer, ReactJS, MDBReact(Material UI), React-Router-DOM, ChartJS, Axios

Food Nomad

Food Nomad is an app that advocates the sharing of recipes, lifehacks and excess ingredients among individuals to reduce food waste.

Tech Stack:

ExpressJS, EJS, MongoDB, Mongoose, Bcrypt, Sessions, Multer, Cloudinary, Google Maps API, OneMap API

Missile Command

A browser-based game inspired by the 1980 Atari arcade classic. 6 cities are being bombarded by countless warheads. It is up to you, to defend the cities by shooting them down.

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Canvas, AJAX

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineering Student | General Assembly

Nov 2020 - Jun 2021

- Building strong foundational knowledge in fullstack web development using modern stacks and frameworks. (MongoDB, Express, React, NodeJs, Django, PostgreSQL)

Terrain Engineer | ST Engineering, Training and Simulations

Nov 2017 - Present

- Led a team of three 3D artists in 2020 to deliver and integrate multiple large-scale 3D terrains
- Created procedural modeling scripts to build and automate processes to scale terrain production from 1km sq to 5km sq.
- Initiate changes in asset workflow such as an asset management system, initiated creation of project repository and custom scripted tools. Reduced average production time by 25%.

3D Generalist | Lights and Shadows Pte Ltd

May 2017 - Aug 2017

- Designed, animated, and lit key sequences which are featured in the studio's highlight reel.
- High-poly cinematic modeler, character/crowd animator, lighting and rendering artist.

3D Modeler | ST Engineering | Internship

Sep 2016 - Feb 2017

- -- "Letter of Appreciation" awarded for the work and effort recognized by the Company.
- Created automation scripts to increase workflow efficiency and led to a higher asset production rate.
- Independently built and troubleshoot assets for 3D simulation.
- Rigged and provided animation cycles for vehicles and organic assets
- Created game-ready 3D assets for aircraft simulators

INTERESTS

Disruptive Innovations | Fintech | Blockchain | Environment | A.I | Sci-Fi | Video Games